my.com 2008-10-10

# My.com

**Privacy Statement**

This privacy statement was last revised on **07/17/2008**. To contact us, please go to “How To Contact Us” in the table of contents below.

**Table of Contents**

Who We Are

What This Document Is

Our Commitment to Privacy

The Information We Collect

Other Members Information

Invite A Friend

The Technologies We Use

The Way We Use Information

Sharing of Your Information

Disclosure Requirements

Links to Third-Party Web Sites

Our Commitment to Data Security

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Opt-Out Policy

How To Access Or Correct Your Information

Changes To This Statement

How To Contact Us

**Who We Are**

My.com is an online community where people can meet to share common interests. In this privacy statement, we may refer to ourselves as “My.com,” “we,” or “us.” In each case, we are referring to My.com or the owner of the website, My Acquisition Corporation. When we talk about our website or our other online services in this policy, we will use the term “our website.” 

**What This Document Is**

This document is our Privacy Statement. It states what information we collect from users of our website, how we use that information, who we share it with, how you can access or change your information, how you can contact us, and other important information about how we safeguard our users’ privacy. Importantly, this statement is a part of our “Terms of Service,” which is the contract that governs our relationship with you, as a visitor to our website. PLEASE NOTE: There are very important terms and conditions governing our relationship that are found in our “terms of service,” that are not repeated here in our privacy statement because they do not relate to data collection or privacy. To see the terms and conditions that govern our relationship with you, go to <http://www.my.com/cms/terms>. 

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

We take privacy seriously.  As a leading social networking company, we are committed to establishing and maintaining policies and procedures which protect the privacy of personal information gathered from visitors to our website. 

**The Information We Collect:**

A Member of our site is a person who has registered to use one or more of the services as described in our terms of service. All other people who view our website are Visitors.

We collect certain Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) from Members of our site, such as your full name, address, and email address that you voluntarily submit in order to become a Member. We also may collect other PII, such as a credit card number should you choose to register for contests, surveys, or additional services that we may offer to our Members. 

In addition, we collect other non-PII, such as IP addresses, aggregate user data, and the type of browser you use to view our website from both Members and Visitors. 

If you are a Member you may also choose to provide or store other non-PII in your profile, including date of birth, interests, hobbies, lifestyle choices, political, social, or business groups with whom you are affiliated, videos and pictures, private messages, bulletins, statements, or blogs.  You provide this information at your sole discretion.

If you are a Member you can change your PII and the non-PII information in your profile at any time, and can control how Visitors and other Members communicate with you by controlling your account settings, available within the “Dashboard” portion of your Member page.

One of the services we offer to Members and Visitors is a front-end, single sign-on to multiple third party Instant Messaging (IM) tools. In order to access your third party IM accounts automatically, we need to store your user name and password to those third party accounts. We do not use this information for any purpose other than to allow you as a Member or Visitor to access third party IM accounts through the My.com website.

You can purchase items, such as virtual gifts, over the web from our website. To facilitate the transaction, we request personal information necessary for billing or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card information.  

**Other Members Information**

You should be aware that Members or Visitors may reveal personal information while communicating on other areas of the My.com website, such as while participating in discussions of posting information to your profile or blogs. This information, in turn, might be viewed by other Members or visitors to the My.com website who are not Members.

**Invite a Friend  
**  
If a Member elects to use our "Invite" feature to invite a friend to become a Member of the My.com website, we ask them for the friend's email address. My.com will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the site. My.com stores this email address for the purpose of automatically adding the respondent to the friends list of the Member sending the invitation, and also to send reminders of the invitation. My.com will never sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. Any person who receives an invitation may contact My.com by filling out the form at [www.my.com/cms/contactus](http://www.my.com/cms/contactus) to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**The Technologies We Use**

Our website uses “cookies” and “log files” to allow you to sign into our services, and to customize your user experience.

A “cookie” is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. The information in the cookie can be read by other web servers within the same domain. A cookie cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses on your computer. 

A “log file” is a file we maintain on our server, that lists technical information about people who visit our site. It is in the log file that we store the technical information we described above, that is, IP address, browser type, language, and referring web page.

**The Way We Use Information**

We never use or share the personal information you provide to us online other than as described below without first giving you a chance to opt out, or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. We do not supplement personally identifiable information with information from any other sources.

We use the personal information you provide to us online:

  * To ensure our website is relevant to your needs by evaluating the effectiveness of our products and services. 
  * To deliver services, such as newsletters that you request or purchase. 
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you. 
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from us. 
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate.
  * To send important status and service messages regarding our website.

For any of the uses of your information that we describe above, you may opt out, and forbid our use of the information for that purpose, by calling, mailing, or emailing us. To find our contact information, please see the “Contact Us” section at the end of this statement. The only information a user cannot opt out of is service updates, which are important notices about the status of the website.

**Sharing of Your Information**

In general, we do not share Members PII or non-PII with third parties. However, we may share your PII with third-parties who help us manage or provide our services, for example, message board administrators. We may also share your information with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with the administration, judging, and prize fulfillment of contests we may run. We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. However, this information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Disclosure Requirements**

Any personal information you submit to us may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders. Additionally, we may access or disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary to: (a) comply with the law, or legal process served on us; (b) protect and defend our legal rights or our property, including enforcement of any agreements; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our clients, employees, partners, or members of the public.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

Our website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

Our website has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the data under our control. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that your information is safe, secure, and available only to you. We also implement an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and host our website in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Finally, we provide unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a customer logs on to our software. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of your information.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

We believe that protecting the privacy of children is especially important. Therefore we do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children under the age of 13, and no part of our website or software is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you are a parent, and believe that we have stored personal identification about your child under the age of 13, please contact us, and we will immediately investigate, and delete any personal information we may have stored about that child.

**Opt-Out Policy  
**  
We offer our visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering our products, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply email or write us. You can find our contact information in the “Contact Us” section at the end of this statement.

From time to time we send promotional materials or newsletters by email, as described above in “The Way We Use Information.” Any email you receive from us will include an “unsubscribe” link that you can use to prohibit us from sending any additional information, and our postal address.

**How To Access Or Correct Your Information**

If you are a Member, you can access your information, and change it as follows:

                1\. From your dashboard, click the “profile” link.

                2\. Select the “[edit]” link next to your name, or the “[edit]” link next to the “About Me” section of the profile to edit your information.

Your information will be changed in our records, and the screen should update to reflect this new information.

If you have contacted us by email, or you are a Member, and the above method does not work, please email or write us. You can find our contact information in the “Contact Us” section at the end of this statement.

**Changes to This Statement**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this statement, we will revise the “last revised” date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement, or material changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing them, and giving you the option to opt-out of the new policy or procedures, or by sending you a notification of the changes directly, prior to implementing them. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to stay informed about how My.com collects and uses your private information. You can always view and print the most recent version of this privacy statement at <http://www.my.com/cms/policy>.

**How To Contact Us**

We welcome your comments regarding this privacy statement, and our privacy practices. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us. You can contact us by email or by regular mail.

**web:**     <http://www.my.com/cms/contactus>

**mail:**     My Acquisition Corporation

            44075 Pipeline Plaza, Suite 320

            Ashburn, VA 20147
